(Sheldon:)Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Welcome to Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun With Flags.
(Sheldon:)My apologies
that this episode is coming late.
(Sheldon:)I did shoot one last week
in honor of Black History Month...
(Sheldon:)...but I was informed by my roommate
that my spot-on portrayal...
(Sheldon:)...of George Washington Carver
could be considered "wildly racist."
(Sheldon:)My heart goes out to the members
of the African-American community...
(Sheldon:)...who, like me,
have been kept down by the man.
(Sheldon:)Now, Fun With Flags
is not just for the flag aficionado...
(Sheldon:)...it's also for the flag novice.
(Sheldon:)So to help me with that, please welcome
my friend, neighbor and flag virgin...
(Sheldon:)...not a real virgin.
(Sheldon:)She's had coitus many times.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes within earshot
of this flag enthusiast.